Finding Aid for the Lamar Alexander Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Series XII: Harvard Teaching Materials
  - Sub-series E: Research Materials
    - Harvard Teaching Materials – Research Materials, 1994-2001
      - Inc., 2001 February 27 (Box 479, Folder 17)
      - Newsweek, 1999 June 28 (Box 479, Folder 18)
      - The Public Perspective, 1997 February-March (Box 479, Folder 19)
      - The New York Times Magazine, 2000 May 7 (Box 479, Folder 20)
      - Time, 1999 June 14 (Box 479, Folder 21)
    - Harvard Teaching Materials – Research Materials, 1996-2001
      - Harvard Educational Review, 1996 Winter (Box 480, Folder 1)
      - The American Enterprise, 2001 January-February (Box 480, Folder 2)
      - “The Global Education Industry – Lessons from Private Education in Developing Countries”, 1999 (Box 480, Folder 3)
      - “Education Reform 1995-1996”, 1996 August (Box 480, Folder 4)
      - “The Super”, 2001 June (Box 480, Folder 5)
      - Notes on Secretary of Education, 2000 (Box 480, Folder 6)
      - “Bystanders to Genocide – Why the United States Let the Rwandan Tragedy Happen”, 2001 September (Box 480, Folder 7)
      - Presidential Addresses, 2001 November (Box 480, Folder 8)
      - PBS Ordering Brochure, undated (Box 480, Folder 9)
      - CATO Publications, 2000-2001 (Box 480, Folder 10)
      - “Metro Public Schools: Preparing Students Now for the Future”, circa 1999 (Box 480, Folder 11)
      - Education Matters, a Journal of Opinion and Research, 2001 Spring (Box 480, Folder 12)
      - Time Magazine – “The American Presidents”, circa 1976 (Box 480, Folder 13)
      - Commentary, 1998 March (Box 480, Folder 14)
      - Time Magazine Special Issue, 1997 Spring (Box 480, Folder 15)
      - Time Magazine Special Issue, 2001 June 11 (Box 480, Folder 16)
      - “Reflections on the Distinctive Character of American Labor Laws” Photocopies, undated (Box 480, Folder 17)
      - “Centering America – Resurrecting the Local Progressive Ideal”, 2001 (Box 480, Folder 18)
      - Notes and Correspondence, 2001 (Box 480, Folder 19)
      - PBS – The American Experience, undated (Box 480, Folder 20)
      - American Enterprise Institute, 2000-2001 (Box 480, Folder 21)
      - Miller Center Report, 2001 Summer (Box 480, Folder 22)
    - Harvard Teaching Materials – Research Materials, 1995-2001
      - Heritage Speech, 1995-1996 (Box 481, Folder 1)
      - National Geographic, 2000 January (Box 481, Folder 2)
      - Campaign for a New American Century Planning Meeting, 1997 June 4-5 (1 of 2) (Box 481, Folder 3)
      - Campaign for a New American Century Planning Meeting, 1997 June 4-5 (2 of 2) (Box 481, Folder 4)
      - Plaid Pass, undated (Box 481, Folder 5)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1998-2001 (1 of 4) (Box 481, Folder 6)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1998-2001 (2 of 4) (Box 481, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1998-2001 (3 of 4) (Box 481, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Newspaper Clippings, 1998-2001 (4 of 4) (Box 481, Folder 9)